[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "What's the address and your emergency?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "address", "and", "your", "emergency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "Yes, ma'am, I'm on 2nd Avenue in the school and the gentleman said tell them to hold down the police officers are coming, he's going to start shooting.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "ma'am", ",", "I", "'m", "on", "2nd", "Avenue", "in", "the", "school", "and", "the", "gentleman", "said", "tell", "them", "to", "hold", "down", "the", "police", "officers", "are", "coming", ",", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "start", "shooting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Tell them to stop all movement.", "answer_tokens": ["Tell", "them", "to", "stop", "all", "movement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Martin, that really was quite remarkable to listen to, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Martin", ",", "that", "really", "was", "quite", "remarkable", "to", "listen", "to", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "Absolutely, I mean, that woman is a one-person crisis negotiating team and what is remarkable is that -- it's almost as if that was the role she was born to play on that particular day.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "that", "woman", "is", "a", "one-person", "crisis", "negotiating", "team", "and", "what", "is", "remarkable", "is", "that", "--", "it", "'s", "almost", "as", "if", "that", "was", "the", "role", "she", "was", "born", "to", "play", "on", "that", "particular", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Do we know anything else about her from the school or from anybody else?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "know", "anything", "else", "about", "her", "from", "the", "school", "or", "from", "anybody", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "No, school officials have not revealed a great deal about her.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "school", "officials", "have", "not", "revealed", "a", "great", "deal", "about", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "How many more times is this kind of thing going to happen before somebody somewhere takes action to try and stop at least some of it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "more", "times", "is", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "going", "to", "happen", "before", "somebody", "somewhere", "takes", "action", "to", "try", "and", "stop", "at", "least", "some", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, you know, unfortunately, Piers, we've had this conversation many times over the last year, and the answer is, it's going to be too many times.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "unfortunately", ",", "Piers", ",", "we", "'ve", "had", "this", "conversation", "many", "times", "over", "the", "last", "year", ",", "and", "the", "answer", "is", ",", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "too", "many", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What is your reaction to that story?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "story", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Well, it's horrific.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "horrific", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "How do you tackle this stream of disenfranchised, disaffected, perhaps deranged young -- they're usually white males who commit these mass shootings or have the intent to commit them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "tackle", "this", "stream", "of", "disenfranchised", ",", "disaffected", ",", "perhaps", "deranged", "young", "--", "they", "'re", "usually", "white", "males", "who", "commit", "these", "mass", "shootings", "or", "have", "the", "intent", "to", "commit", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", ",", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "It's very, very difficult to do it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", ",", "very", "difficult", "to", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Well, I think there is a lot of polarization here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "is", "a", "lot", "of", "polarization", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Is that a new prong in your attack?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "new", "prong", "in", "your", "attack", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Sure, we have to keep up with the times and clearly social media is being used to change information, actually to show pictures of guns that were for sale.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "we", "have", "to", "keep", "up", "with", "the", "times", "and", "clearly", "social", "media", "is", "being", "used", "to", "change", "information", ",", "actually", "to", "show", "pictures", "of", "guns", "that", "were", "for", "sale", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Wouldn't that make life easier for everyone in your kind of position as city police chief, just have the same rule in every state relating to guns?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "that", "make", "life", "easier", "for", "everyone", "in", "your", "kind", "of", "position", "as", "city", "police", "chief", ",", "just", "have", "the", "same", "rule", "in", "every", "state", "relating", "to", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "What is it about the gun itself, the culture of gun ownership, perhaps, which makes it so difficult to have this kind of sensible view of guns around the nation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "the", "gun", "itself", ",", "the", "culture", "of", "gun", "ownership", ",", "perhaps", ",", "which", "makes", "it", "so", "difficult", "to", "have", "this", "kind", "of", "sensible", "view", "of", "guns", "around", "the", "nation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Well I think a lot of people simply aren't affected by guns.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "simply", "are", "n't", "affected", "by", "guns", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Do you think stop-and-frisk is deliberate racial profiling but for a purpose that is, in your eyes, worth doing and successful?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "stop-and-frisk", "is", "deliberate", "racial", "profiling", "but", "for", "a", "purpose", "that", "is", ",", "in", "your", "eyes", ",", "worth", "doing", "and", "successful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "No, it's certainly not racial profiling.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "certainly", "not", "racial", "profiling", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Why is this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "It's a story that's largely been blown up in the media and not exactly accurate.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "story", "that", "'s", "largely", "been", "blown", "up", "in", "the", "media", "and", "not", "exactly", "accurate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Is that, as far as you know, true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", ",", "as", "far", "as", "you", "know", ",", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "There is a lot of speculation.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "a", "lot", "of", "speculation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim"]}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "But was she -- but, Andrew, was she aware, Laura, of any relationship between Christina Anderson and Jim DiMaggio?", "question_tokens": ["But", "was", "she", "--", "but", ",", "Andrew", ",", "was", "she", "aware", ",", "Laura", ",", "of", "any", "relationship", "between", "Christina", "Anderson", "and", "Jim", "DiMaggio", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "We know that the relationship was that Jim played a very key role in the family and was seen as an uncle, obviously.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "know", "that", "the", "relationship", "was", "that", "Jim", "played", "a", "very", "key", "role", "in", "the", "family", "and", "was", "seen", "as", "an", "uncle", ",", "obviously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andrew", "Christina Anderson", "Jim DiMaggio"], "LOCATION": ["Laura"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "How did that make you feel, the collective pressure that she was clearly being put under?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", ",", "the", "collective", "pressure", "that", "she", "was", "clearly", "being", "put", "under", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Well, I can tell you that I had a very close relationship with my daughter.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "that", "I", "had", "a", "very", "close", "relationship", "with", "my", "daughter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "What is the lesson, the warning do you think to other parents that comes out of this awful tragedy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "lesson", ",", "the", "warning", "do", "you", "think", "to", "other", "parents", "that", "comes", "out", "of", "this", "awful", "tragedy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "If anything, I think you need to keep tabs on your children's activity on the Internet.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "anything", ",", "I", "think", "you", "need", "to", "keep", "tabs", "on", "your", "children", "'s", "activity", "on", "the", "Internet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Audrie"]}, "docId": "130821pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "Bob Allard, in terms of the law surrounding all this, what are the issues that have been raised and does the law do enough do you think in situations like this?", "question_tokens": ["Bob", "Allard", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "law", "surrounding", "all", "this", ",", "what", "are", "the", "issues", "that", "have", "been", "raised", "and", "does", "the", "law", "do", "enough", "do", "you", "think", "in", "situations", "like", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "Well, civilly we intend to prove that the actions of these young men and young woman was a main factor why Audrie did what she did, and civilly, we intend to prove that those actions did lead to her death.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "civilly", "we", "intend", "to", "prove", "that", "the", "actions", "of", "these", "young", "men", "and", "young", "woman", "was", "a", "main", "factor", "why", "Audrie", "did", "what", "she", "did", ",", "and", "civilly", ",", "we", "intend", "to", "prove", "that", "those", "actions", "did", "lead", "to", "her", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Allard"]}}]